<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Venu&#39;s Webstrings</title>
    <link>https://tnvmadhav.surge.sh/posts/</link>
    <description>T Venu Madhav&#39;s personal website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020  T Venu Madhav
All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 18:18:59 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tnvmadhav.surge.sh/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>🕛 Time Progress App</title>
        <link>https://tnvmadhav.surge.sh/posts/time-progress-app/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 18:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://tnvmadhav.surge.sh/posts/time-progress-app/</guid>
        <description>&amp;ldquo;Progress is being made&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; It would be really cool to stamp milestones for various types of progress. It could be anything from a projects, careers to vacations. Timestamps are often used to plot the beginning of something and the expected time for something yet to happen or develop. Timestamps can be put on anything to literally mark events into our calendar. It gives us humans clarity about what can and cannot be done in project/life management.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why did the founding titan renounce war? 🤯</title>
        <link>https://tnvmadhav.surge.sh/posts/theory-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 15:20:46 +0530</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://tnvmadhav.surge.sh/posts/theory-time/</guid>
        <description>Alternatively, you can refer to the following youtube video,   
 Yes, we are in the end game now as the alliance have taken off to their impending doom. This is where we as the Attack on Titan/SnK fandom adjust ourselves, lean forward into the various interesting directions Isayama could take the narrative.
But the closer we get to the end, more theories leave the realm of possibilities into either oblivion or reality.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Getting Oneself to Do It</title>
        <link>https://tnvmadhav.surge.sh/posts/getting-one-to-do-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 09:57:56 +0530</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://tnvmadhav.surge.sh/posts/getting-one-to-do-it/</guid>
        <description>When you have an idea which you think would look and feel cool after the said execution, you immediately google the hell out of it. You try to connect the dots and then you stumble upon some github repositories doing the same thing but better. You shake your head for a minute and move on.
What? Yes. Deep inside you know it that your idea was original so you feel a bit defeated&amp;hellip;life feels useless and you want it to change but you don&amp;rsquo;t know how or where to start.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Character Study Eren Jaeger</title>
        <link>https://tnvmadhav.surge.sh/posts/character-study-eren-jaeger/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 22:03:39 +0530</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://tnvmadhav.surge.sh/posts/character-study-eren-jaeger/</guid>
        <description>“Set your heart upon your work but never its reward.” – Lord Krishna   The last plow felt even better. The soil was as moist as it was when he used to play in it when he was five. The two-acre field was enough to provide him two seasons worth of food and supplies. He invested half of his life savings in industrial tools that he felt were prevalent at the time.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello There! 👋</title>
        <link>https://tnvmadhav.surge.sh/posts/my-first-post/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 15:55:52 +0530</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://tnvmadhav.surge.sh/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
        <description>Just checking in! If you see this, then you do not need to worry! 😄</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>